[
  [
    {
      "question": "This anime character picked Pikachu as his first Pokemon in the TV show's first episode",
      "answer": "Ash Ketchum",
      "points": "200"
    },
    {
      "question": "This character is the primary antagoinst of the Legend of Zelda series",
      "answer": "Ganon/Ganondorf",
      "points": "200"
    },
    {
      "question": "This boy group member is most recently famous for his hit song 'Seven' and '3D' featuring Jack Harlow",
      "answer": "BTS Jungkook",
      "points": "200"
    },
    {
      "question": "Finish the meme: 'Two bros chilling in a hot tub five feet apart cause they're not ___'",
      "answer": "Gay",
      "points": "200"
    },
    {
      "question": "This marvel villain sought to retrieve all five infinity stones to half the universe's population",
      "answer": "Thanos",
      "points": "200"
    },
    {
      "question": "Lyric has two dogs. What are their names?",
      "answer": "Belle and Bean",
      "points": "200"
    }
  ],
  [
    {
      "question": "This anime character had just recently shown up as their own balloon in this year's Macy's parade",
      "answer": "Monkey D. Luffy",
      "points": "400"
    },
    {
      "question": "This system brought Microsoft into the gaming world. It is also considered the system with a game that modernized the first person shooter",
      "answer": "Xbox",
      "points": "400"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the girl group Le Sserafim's name an anagram of?",
      "answer": "I'm Fearless",
      "points": "400"
    },
    {
      "question": "This teen internet viral sensation has a very limited selection of white shoes.",
      "answer": "Damn Daniel",
      "points": "400"
    },
    {
      "question": "Who killed Tony Stark's parents in the MCU?",
      "answer": "Bucky Barnes",
      "points": "400"
    },
    {
      "question": "What special name did Maddie give to her Lumpfishes at the Aquarium?",
      "answer": "The Lumpias",
      "points": "400"
    }
  ],
  [
    {
      "question": "In Attack of Titan, it is revealed at the end of the first season that the walls are actually made out of what?",
      "answer": "Colossal Titans",
      "points": "600"
    },
    {
      "question": "In this online game, you play as an 'agent' and try to defuse/plant a spike on enemy territory",
      "answer": "Valorant",
      "points": "600"
    },
    {
      "question": "Name at least 5 members from the girl group Twice",
      "answer": "Momo, Sana, Mina, Dahyun, Nayeon, Jihyo, Tzuyu, Chaeyoung, Jeongyeon",
      "points": "600"
    },
    {
      "question": "Comprised of block colors, this cartonn animal's right limb has been used to express anger or frustration.",
      "answer": "Arthur",
      "points": "600"
    },
    {
      "question": "What does E.D.I.T.H stand for?",
      "answer": "Even Dead, I am the Hero",
      "points": "600"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is James currently majoring in?",
      "answer": "Electrical Engineering",
      "points": "600"
    }
  ],
  [
    {
      "question": "The eight primary villanious forces of the Full Metal Alchemist series. These people are basically immortal and are powered by a Philosopher's stone.",
      "answer": "Homonculus",
      "points": "800"
    },
    {
      "question": "In Baldur's Gate 3, what race and class is Karlach's character associated with?",
      "answer": "Tiefling Barbarian",
      "points": "800"
    },
    {
      "question": "This unique take on a girl group which comprises of seven members, all of whom are Japanese, sing their songs in English, and market themselves as a 'Korean' pop group",
      "answer": "XG",
      "points": "800"
    },
    {
      "question": "A popular meme comic format from the early 2010s, comprising of crudely drawn cartoon faces expressing several different emotions. Among these were face like 'Forever Alone' or the 'Troll face'",
      "answer": "Rage Comics",
      "points": "800"
    },
    {
      "question": "The only movie in the MCU that is NOT an Avengers movie, yet features most of the Avengers",
      "answer": "Captain America Civil War",
      "points": "800"
    },
    {
      "question": "What does Moises do for work?",
      "answer": "Paraeducator",
      "points": "800"
    }
  ],
  [
    {
      "question": "Other than Devil Fruits, what is the other primary power system in One Piece?",
      "answer": "Haki",
      "points": "1000"
    },
    {
      "question": "This console released in 1988, rivaling Nintendo and jump started the career of a certain speedy hedgehog",
      "answer": "Sega Genesis",
      "points": "1000"
    },
    {
      "question": "NewJeans' single OMG just exceeded how many streams on Spotify?",
      "answer": "1 Billion",
      "points": "1000"
    },
    {
      "question": "This dearly departed primate recieved over 16,000 votes in the 2016 US election",
      "answer": "Harambe",
      "points": "1000"
    },
    {
      "question": "What multiverse code is the MCU assigned to?",
      "answer": "Earth-199999",
      "points": "1000"
    },
    {
      "question": "Hugo's favorite Pluto Koi song",
      "answer": "Just Ghosts",
      "points": "1000"
    }
  ]
]
